Uh... w-well...
Okay, look, I-I don't
want to lie to you.
I-I got curious,
I was looking around...
(Raj:)and I broke the drawer
on your night stand.
(Emily:)You were looking
in my night stand?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Emily:)So, the first time
I leave you alone,
(Emily:)you snoop on me?
(Raj:)You've never snooped
around my apartment?
No!
Come on, think back.
It would really help if you had!
EMILY: I can't believe
you don't trust me!
(Bernadette:)She sounds really mad.
(Howard:)We should hang up.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, we should.
(Howard:)But we're not
going to, are we?
(Bernadette:)Not a chance.
(Howard:)What happened to
"snooping is wrong"?
(Bernadette:)Howard, you're going
to jail for tax fraud.
(Bernadette:)Who cares?
(Leonard:)Well, we did it.
(Penny:)We sure did.
I mean, I was on fire!
I-I was in the zone,
like an athlete.
(Penny:)Sweetie, I beat
you at this, too.
(Leonard:)So, where do we
want to hang it?